<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Learn X</string>
    <string name="speech_app_name">LRL Speech Recognition</string>
    <string name="title_datum_detail">Datum</string>
    <string name="app_explanation">
      Field linguists and open source developers have gotten together to create a
      speech recognizer for low resource language speakers. You can use this
      application to prepare your Android to guess your speech. You need to read some
      suggestions and then contact WiFi in order to prepare your voice model. We
      expect that after reading some training sentences you will have a better result.
      Because low resource languages are different from other languages ​​so we do
      not know how useful this application will be. You can try it, it is mostly
      experimental and used for research, so we can not guarantee that it will be
      useful. If you use the app to train your recognizer, you agree that we can
      use the anonymous training recordings to improve the recognizer and for linguistics research.
      Here's our resulting research: http://batumi.github.io
      We don't use or share your private data with anyone. Here is our privacy policy:
      https://www.lingsync.org/privacy.html
    </string>
    <string name="are_you_sure">Are you sure?</string>
    <string name="are_you_sure_put_in_trash">Are you sure you want to put this datum in the trash?</string>

    <!-- Recognition prompts -->
    <string name="im_listening">I\'m listening</string>
    <string name="i_might_have_heard">I might have heard: </string>
    <string name="or_maybe">Or maybe this: </string>
    <string name="there_were_others">. I\'m pretty funny, ey? There were some other options, but I think I\'ll stop there. </string>
    <string name="train">Train</string>
    <string name="recognize">Recognize</string>
    <string name="tap_to_speak">Tap to speak again</string>
    <string name="tap_to_end">Tap to end</string>
    <string name="speak_now">Speak now</string>
    <string name="dialog_continue_to_advanced_training">Add your own words?</string>
    <string name="continue_word">Continue</string>
    <string name="finished">Enough</string>
    <string name="context">Context</string>
    <string name="orthography">Words</string>
    <string name="tag_hint">WebSearch, SMS, Email</string>
    <string name="translation_hint"></string>
    <string name="remove">Remove</string>
    <string name="no_recognized_result">I didn\'t hear anything...</string>
    <string name="hypothesis">Hypothesis</string>
    <string name="training_instructions">You need to read a few sentences to train the recognizer to your voice and your words</string>
    <string name="training_context">
      The Georgian language is very complex and very different from other languages
      which were used to build Speech Recognition systems. This means each person
      should have their own recognizer.
    </string>
    <string name="title_datum_list_activity">Recognition Trainer Advanced</string>

</resources>
